{
    "id": "bd3c2c9da7344708998d7056fccec26b",
    "title": "Opposites Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Coffee is a stimulant while opium is a .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "retardant",
                "sedative",
                "pacifier"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec0dbc4b0e5a407987b4a1ed1f84b3b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The peacock is beautiful, but the ostrich is .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ugly",
                "plain",
                "clumsy",
                "dirty"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "36022d3c5eb144a9b94d6aaa1a40e68c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tiger is carnivorous whereas the cow is .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "viviparous",
                "omnivorous",
                "herbivorous"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1b33f36f14ca4a8d8fa07945d0f20e32"
        },
        {
            "question": "The like poles of a magnet …………………. while unlike poles attract.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "detest",
                "rival",
                "repel",
                "disgust"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7ea9327c5dd3466f85b73fe7a3eaf55d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Love is a virtue while hatred is a .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wise",
                "vise",
                "vice"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e7f8d70878e94d24917dc120f8852875"
        },
        {
            "question": "The road ascends to the top of the hill and then ...................... to the plain on the other side.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "condescends",
                "concedes",
                "descends"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3b7de906d4324846a564b3ac1addfe0c"
        },
        {
            "question": "These rules are too rigid. We need more .....................… ones.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lucid",
                "timid",
                "flexible"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d6ae74538cbb4bc3a0f2430a2147b08b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kindness is admired, but cruelty is .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wicked",
                "despised",
                "disgusted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "acb9feb316f44d9b96c9ae014c007684"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some parts are separable from the whole and some are .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "imseparable",
                "unseparable",
                "inseparable"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bb817246edcc4cf4a5f655bd2eaaf73d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should not oppose or ....................... a government blindly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "approve",
                "support",
                "join",
                "disapprove"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7907e20d7cd544d484b32dc4f5fcef9a"
        }
    ]
}